

Juan José Sarasola

Personal Profile

I have over nine years of experience in IT, including end users assistance, server management and more complex troubleshooting. I am interested in continuing my development in the IT field while I deepen my knowledge in programming.

Competencies

- Problem Solving.
- · Teamwork.
- Internet Savvy.
- · Analytical mind.

IT Skills

- Networking (Mikrotik, pfSense, WireGuard)
- Microsoft OS products (Windows 10, Office 365).
- Windows Server 2008/2012/2016/2019
- · Linux Servers: Debian/CentOS
- MySQL/MongoDB
- Git
- HTML5/CSS/JavaScript/NodeJS/React/VueJS
- ServiceNow/Zendesk/Jira Ticketing System.
- Zabbix.
- Virtualization products (VMware ESXI).
- Docker.

Languages

- · Spanish (native)
- English (advanced)

Personal & Contact Details

Age: 32

Nationality: Argentina/Spanish

Location: Madrid, Spain. Mobile: +34 674436790 WhatsApp: +5491169954752 Email: jjsarasola@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/jjsarasola/



github.com/jjsarasola/

Work Experience

IOV LABS

Customer Support Specialist in the Integration & Support Team Janury 2022 - Present

- Provide customer support to partners and end users of the Rootstock blockchain network.
- Testing and troubleshooting of network nodes using Docker containers.
- Content writing for the official docs of the Help Desk website and KB.
- Management of the customer support bot. This bot was developed by me using NodeJS and MongoDB to interact with users using Slack and Discord APIs.

BARAGHOST

IT Analyst

March 2018 - Janury 2022

- Server administration (Windows Server and Linux).
- Network administration (Firewalls, LANs, VPN).
- Monitor ISP links and servers. (Zabbix).
- Manage Web Hostings and DNS. (WHM/CPanel)
- Manage Google Workspace (ex G Suite).
- Manage OVH Cloud services (Servers, Failover IPs).

SMART WAY

IT Support Technician for Adecco Argentina February 2020 - July 2020

- Provide help desk service to internal client by email, chat and phone.
- Manage tickets in ServiceNow (e.g. events, incidents and requests, inventory).
- Workstations support (Microsoft).
- Active Directory.
- Server management (Windows Server & Linux).

INTERMEDIA SP

IT Support Technician February 2010 - March 2018

- Provide help desk service to end users by email, chat and phone.
- Manage tickets in Zendesk (e.g. events, incidents and requests).
- Monitor ISP links and servers.
- Deliver set ups (workstations).
- Set up and manage servers and networks in the datacenter.

References

• IOV Labs

Alejandro Cavallero (Head of Integrations and

Support)

Mobile: +54 1141874000 Email: +54 5199-4028

BARAGHOST

Bohdan Yakushenko (Manager)

Mobile: +54 1141874000 Telephone: +54 5199-4028

• Smart Way

Martín Lukacs (Manager) Mobile: +54 1138407082

• Santiago Del Bono (IT Director - Adecco Arg.)

Mobile: +54 1132120392

• Intermedia SP Federico Greco

Mobile: +54 1161133202

Educational background

• EDUCACIÓN IT

2019 - 2020 JavaScript FullStack Developer. Completed.

• UTN

2020-2022 Android Studio Developer Course (Kotlin). Completed.

• UNIVERSIDAD DE BUENOS AIRES

2010 - 2016

Lawyer. Completed.